a herd of sheep grazing in a field
Vista Aèria d’un Ramat de Bestiar Nelore
a wolf standing in the middle of a forest
Llop en la Natura
a cat sitting in the snow on a snowy day
Gat Domèstic Marró
a red deer stag in a rut with hinds
Cérvol Roig Mascle en Època de Brama amb Cérvoles
a red fox standing next to a tree
Guineu Roja al Bosc
a ram standing on a hillside
Íbex Alpí a la Muntanya
a white polar wolf sitting on top of a rock
Família de Llops Àrtics
a red panda is sitting on a log near a tree
Panda Vermell Menjant
a brown and white striped tiger standing next to a tree
Tigre de Sibèria Cridant la seva Parella
an elephant walking through a grassy field
Elefant Llançant Terra sobre Ell
a brown and white squirrel eating some grass
Esquirol Vermell
a deer walking through a forest with a bunch of trees
Cérvol Salvatge al Bosc
a brown and black lizard sitting on a rock
Llangardaix Dragó Bàrbut
a frame of a bee hive
Panoràmica d’un Rusc
a giraffe walking in the savannah
Girafa Caminant per la Sabana
a herd of sheep grazing on a lush green hillside
Vista Aèria d’un Ramat de Bestiar Nelore
a brown and white striped tiger laying on a dirt ground
Tigre Reial de Bengala
a small black bear is standing in the trees
Gibó Platejat Forrajejant
a large black and white photo of a gorilla
Goril·la de les Planures Occidentals
a large owl sitting on top of a tree branch
Òliba de Banyes Llargues
a close up picture of a cute little brown and white cat
Linx Euroasiàtic Enfadat
two young leopards are standing next to each other
Família de Lleopard de les Neus
a small brown cheetah sitting on top of a grass covered field
Guepard Juvenil Vigilant